THANK YOU FOR
THE DELICIOUS DINNER.
YOU'RE WELCOME
FOR THE DELICIOUS DINNER.
HEY! WHAT ARE YOU GUYS
LOOKING AT?
Chandler:
ROSS AND THE MOST BEAUTIFUL
GIRL IN THE WORLD.
YEAH, COME TO PAPA!
I KNOW!
PROBABLY THE ONLY TIME
I'LL EVER SAY THIS
BUT DID YOU SEE
THE ASS ON HER?
WHERE DID YOU...?
WHEN DID YOU...?
HOW DID YOU...?
HOW DID YOU
GET A GIRL LIKE THAT?
YEAH, SO, WHAT IS SHE...
LIKE, A SPOKESMODEL?
AEROBICS INSTRUCTOR? WHAT?
ACTUALLY, SHE'S A PALEONTOLOGY
DOCTORAL CANDIDATE
SPECIALIZING
IN THE CENOZOIC ERA.
OKAY, BUT THAT'S, LIKE,
THE EASIEST ERA.
I'VE SEEN HER AT WORK
BUT I ALWAYS FIGURED...
( snorting )
BUT, UH, I MADE HER DINNER
WE HAD A GREAT TIME
AND WE'RE GOING OUT AGAIN
TOMORROW.
MAYBE SHE AND HER FRIENDS
ARE HAVING A CONTEST
TO SEE WHO BRINGS HOME
THE BIGGEST GEEK.
FINE BY ME.
HOPE SHE WINS.
♪ SO NO ONE TOLD YOU
LIFE WAS GONNA BE THIS WAY ♪
♪ YOUR JOB'S A JOKE,
YOU'RE BROKE ♪
♪ YOUR LOVE LIFE'S D.O.A. ♪
♪ IT'S LIKE YOU'RE ALWAYS
STUCK IN SECOND GEAR ♪
♪ WHEN IT HASN'T BEEN YOUR DAY ♪
♪ YOUR WEEK, YOUR MONTH,
OR EVEN YOUR YEAR ♪
♪ BUT I'LL BE THERE FOR YOU ♪
♪ WHEN THE RAIN
STARTS TO POUR ♪
♪ I'LL BE THERE FOR YOU ♪
♪ LIKE I'VE BEEN THERE BEFORE ♪
♪ 'CAUSE YOU'RE THERE
FOR ME, TOO. ♪
HI. DO YOU GUYS HAVE
ANY WRAPPING PAPER?
OH! IS IT FOR
MY BIRTHDAY PRESENT?
PHEEBS, IT WAS YOUR BIRTHDAY,
LIKE, MONTHS AGO.
YEAH, BUT REMEMBER YOU SAID
YOU ORDERED SOMETHING SPECIAL
AND IT JUST HADN'T COME YET?
WELL, I HAVE A CALL IN
ABOUT THAT.
OH, OKAY.
ACTUALLY, THIS IS FOR
KATHY'S BIRTHDAY.
IT'S AN EARLY EDITION
OF HER FAVORITE BOOK.
OH!
THE VELVETEEN RABBIT.
OH, MY GOD. WHEN THE BOY'S LOVE
MAKES THE RABBIT REAL...
OKAY, BUT DON'T TOUCH IT
BECAUSE YOUR FINGERS HAVE
DESTRUCTIVE OILS.
OH. WELL, THEN YOU BETTER
KEEP IT AWAY FROM ROSS' HAIR.
THIS IS PRETTY RARE.
HOW DID YOU GET THAT?
IT WASN'T A BIG DEAL.
I JUST WENT
TO A COUPLE OF BOOKSTORES
TALKED TO A COUPLE OF DEALERS
CALLED A COUPLE
OF THE AUTHOR'S GRANDCHILDREN.
OH... HONEY, THAT'S SO SWEET.
YEAH, AND WHAT A GREAT WAY
TO SAY, "I SECRETLY LOVE YOU
ROOMMATE'S GIRLFRIEND."
IT DOESN'T SAY THAT.
DOES IT?
HOW DO YOU THINK IT WILL
LOOK WHEN YOU GET HER
SOMETHING INCREDIBLY
MEANINGFUL AND EXPENSIVE
AND HER BOYFRIEND JOEY
GIVES HER AN ORANGE?
OKAY, I'LL JUST MAKE SURE
JOEY GETS HER SOMETHING
REALLY GREAT.
IT'S GOT TO BE BETTER
THAN THAT BOOK.
OOH! LIKE A CROSSBOW!
YEAH.
ONCE AGAIN, I AM SORRY.
THANK YOU. BYE.
I JUST HAD
TO TURN DOWN A JOB
CATERING A FUNERAL
FOR 60 PEOPLE.
( gasping ):
OH, MY GOD!
WHAT HAPPENED?
60 GUESTS.
SO, UH, WHY'D YOU
HAVE TO TURN IT DOWN?
BECAUSE I DON'T HAVE
THE MONEY OR EQUIPMENT
TO HANDLE SOMETHING THAT BIG
ON SUCH SHORT NOTICE.
THERE'S NO WAY.
WHAT IS WITH
ALL THE NEGATIVITY?
YOU SOUND LIKE "MONI CAN'T",
NOT "MONI CAN."
"MONI CA."
YOU HAVE BEEN PLAYING AROUND
WITH CATERING
FOR OVER THREE YEARS.
DO YOU WANT TO BE
A CATERER OR NOT?
I DON'T KNOW.
THERE YOU GO! THAT'S THE SPIRIT!
NOW IF YOU NEED MONEY
I WILL LEND YOU MONEY.
BUT JUST GET MOVING!
REALLY? I NEED $500
FOR FOOD AND SUPPLIES AND STUFF.
IT'S WORTH IT
IF IT'LL GET YOU MOVING.
YOU HAVEN'T WORKED IN MONTHS.
YOU'RE NOT WORKING, EITHER.
YES, BUT I'M DOING THIS.
THAT'D BE GREAT.
THANK YOU.
HEY.
HEY!
CAN I BORROW THE KEYS
TO YOUR APARTMENT?
WHY?
( chuckling )
YOU CAN PEE HERE!
( chuckling nervously )
YES, I CAN.
OF COURSE.
IF YOU'LL EXCUSE ME.
IT'S OKAY.
THE DUCK'S USING
OUR BATHROOM ANYWAY.
HEY, JOE WHAT ARE YOU GETTING
KATHY FOR HER BIRTHDAY?
WE'VE ONLY GONE OUT
A COUPLE OF WEEKS.
YOU THINK I'M
GETTING HER SOMETHING?
YES, YOU HAVE TO GET HER
SOMETHING REALLY NICE.
OH! I KNOW.
AND NOT ONE OF YOUR COUPONS
FOR AN HOUR OF "JOEY LOVE."
OOH! A CROSSWORD!
CAN I HELP?
NO! I'M SORRY, HONEY.
LAST WEEK, I GOT
ALL BUT THREE ANSWERS.
I WANT TO FINISH ONE
WITHOUT HELP.
FINE.
BUT YOU CAN'T HELP ME DEVELOP
MY NEW UNIVERSAL LANGUAGE.
HEY.
HOW'D IT GO?
OH, MY GOD!
IT WAS THE BEST FUNERAL EVER!
EVERYONE LOVED THE FOOD,
AND GUESS WHAT?
I GOT ANOTHER FUNERAL TOMORROW--
THE DEAD GUY FROM TODAY'S
BEST FRIEND.
IT IS LIKE
I AM THE OFFICIAL CATERER
FOR THAT ACCIDENT.
GOD, I'M SO HAPPY FOR YOU!
OH, THANKS.
CHECK OUT MY NEW
CATERING STUFF.
( gasping )
LOOK! I'M AN OMELET STATION!
"OMELET, MADE TO ORDER."
( laughing ):
I'LL HAVE ONE, PLEASE.
PLUS MY MONEY.
OH.
I DIDN'T REALIZE
YOU NEEDED IT BACK RIGHT AWAY.
YOU TOLD ME
TO GO BE A CATERER.
SO I WENT, I BE'D.
I USED IT TO BUY
ALL THIS STUFF.
I GOT ANOTHER
JOB TOMORROW.
I'LL PAY YOU BACK
WITH THE MONEY FROM THAT.
OH! OKAY.
OOH, SORRY I ACTED
LIKE A BANK.
HMM...
UM...
WOULD YOU LIKE TO COME IN?
DID HOMO ERECTUS HUNT
WITH WOODEN TOOLS?
ACCORDING TO RECENT FINDINGS.
( both laughing )
( snorting )
HERE, MITZI!
HERE, MITZI.
UH...
MITZI IS...?
MY HAMSTER.
I HOPE SHE'S OKAY.
I HAVEN'T SEEN HER IN A WHILE.
HAVE A SEAT.
( no audio )
UH... OH, HEY!
DO YOU, UH...
( crunching )
DO YOU HAVE ANY, UM...
CINNAMON FRUIT TOASTIES?
WHAT?
WELL, I DO.
WHY DON'T WE GO BACK
TO MY PLACE
LIGHT A COUPLE OF CANDLES
BREAK OPEN A BOX OF
CINNAMON FRUIT TOASTIES.
I'D RATHER NOT.
OH, YEAH?
WHY NOT?
OKAY, UM...
DON'T TAKE THIS THE WRONG WAY?
BUT YOUR PLACE KIND OF HAS
A WEIRD SMELL.
IS EVERYTHING IN THE CAR?
YEP.
DID YOU SETTLE THE BILL?
NO.
I HATE THIS PART.
( gasping ):
OH! LOOK WHAT WE ALMOST LEFT!
THAT'S NOT MINE.
OH, ALL RIGHT.
OOH! LOOK WHAT WE ALMOST TOOK!
EXCUSE ME, MISS BURKART.
WELL, WE'RE ALL CLEANED UP
IN THE KITCHEN.
OH, GOOD.
THANK YOU.
UM...
( clears throat )
AND, WELL, THERE'S JUST...
THE SMALL MATTER
OF THE, UM...
DEAR?
JUST THE MATTER OF...
THE PAYMENT?
JACK USED TO HANDLE
THE FINANCES.
( sobbing )
( sighing )
YOU KNOW WHAT WE SHOULD ALL DO?
GO SEE A MUSICAL.
SURE.
AND YOU KNOW
WHICH ONE WE SHOULD SEE?
THE 1996 TONY AWARD WINNER.
DO YOU HAPPEN TO KNOW
THE NAME OF THAT ONE?
I DON'T KNOW, UH...
GREASE?
NO.
RENT?
YES!
RENT.
OKAY, SO WHEN DO YOU
WANT TO GO?
WHAT? OH, I'M SORRY,
I CAN'T. I'M BUSY.
HEY.
MAN, IT IS SO HARD
TO SHOP FOR GIRLS.
( groaning )
YES, IT IS--
AT "OFFICE MAX."
WHAT DID YOU GET HER?
A PEN.
IT'S TWO GIFTS IN ONE.
IT'S A PEN THAT'S
ALSO A CLOCK, HUH?
HA-HA!
YOU CAN'T GIVE HER THAT.
WHY NOT?
BECAUSE SHE'S NOT 11!
AND IT'S NOT THE SEVENTH
NIGHT OF CHANUKAH!
HONEY, WHAT HE MEANS IS,
WHILE THIS IS A VERY NICE GIFT
MAYBE IT'S JUST NOT SOMETHING
A BOYFRIEND GIVES?
SURE, IT IS.
SHE NEEDS A PEN FOR WORK
SHE'S WRITING,
SHE TURNS IT OVER--
"WHOA! IT'S TIME FOR
MY DATE WITH JOEY!"
LOOK, WHAT DID YOU GET
FOR ANGELA DELVECCHIO
FOR HER BIRTHDAY?
SHE DIDN'T HAVE A BIRTHDAY
WHILE WE WERE GOING OUT.
FOR THREE YEARS?
WELL, LOOK, IT'S TOO LATE,
AND I GOT AN AUDITION.
( whining ):
I CAN'T SHOP ANYMORE!
ALL RIGHT, I WILL GO OUT
AND I WILL TRY TO FIND
SOMETHING FOR HER, OKAY?
THANKS, MAN.
OH, WHILE YOU'RE AT IT,
COULD YOU GET HER A CARD?
WOULD YOU LIKE ME TO WRITE HER
A LITTLE POEM, AS WELL?
OR JUST GET A CARD
THAT HAS A POEM
ALREADY IN IT.
YOU HAVE TO GET
OUR MONEY!
PHEEBS, SHE COULDN'T
STOP CRYING.
WITH THOSE THICK GLASSES,
HER TEARS LOOKED GIANT.
I KNOW IT'S TOUGH.
YOU KNOW THE FIRST THING I DID
AFTER MY MOTHER'S FUNERAL?
WHAT?
PAY THE CATERER.
LOOK, I'VE HAD
A LOT OF JOBS
AND THERE ARE SOME PEOPLE
WHO JUST ALWAYS TRY
TO GET OUT OF PAYING.
IT'S EITHER, "THAT MASSAGE
WASN'T LONG ENOUGH"
OR, "I DON'T RECOGNIZE
ANY OF THOSE SONGS"
OR, "THESE SOMBREROS
AREN'T BIG ENOUGH.
BAD LITTLE WHITE GIRL."
OKAY.
SO YOU-YOU THINK SHE'S FAKING?
IT SEEMS LIKE
THERE WEREN'T ANY TEARS
TILL YOU SHOWED HER THE BILL.
SHE SOUNDED PRETTY UPSET TO ME.
♪ YOU'RE A GRAND OLD FLAG ♪
♪ YOU'RE A HIGH-FLYIN' FLAG ♪
♪ AND FOREVER IN PEACE
MAY YOU WAVE... ♪
SHE SEEMS FINE NOW.
♪ THE LAND I LOVE ♪
♪ THE HOME OF... ♪
SO YOU JUST LEFT?
HER PLACE WAS
REALLY THAT BAD?
YOU KNOW HOW YOU THROW
YOUR JACKET ON A CHAIR
AT THE END OF THE DAY?
LIKE THAT, ONLY
INSTEAD OF A CHAIR
IT'S A PILE OF GARBAGE.
AND INSTEAD OF A JACKET,
AND INSTEAD OF
THE END OF THE DAY
IT'S THE END OF TIME
AND GARBAGE IS ALL
THAT HAS SURVIVED.
HERE.
WOW. THANKS.
SO, UH, WHAT HAPPENED?
NOTHING HAPPENED.
I HAD TO GET OUT OF THERE.
ALL RIGHT. NEXT TIME,
YOU TAKE HER TO YOUR PLACE.
NO. I TRIED THAT.
SHE SAYS IT HAS A WEIRD SMELL.
WHAT KIND OF SMELL?
I DON'T KNOW-- SOAP?!
ALL RIGHT. LISTEN, ROSS.
YOU LIKE THIS GIRL, RIGHT?
YOU WANT
TO SEE HER AGAIN?
YEAH.
SO YOU'LL HAVE TO DO IT
IN THE MESS!
YEAH, OKAY.
YOU'RE RIGHT.
YEAH.
I MEAN, UH, WHO CARES
ABOUT A LITTLE SLOPPINESS?
YEAH.
IT'S, UH...
IT'S ENDEARING, REALLY.
ALL RIGHT.
NOW, YOU GO GET
THAT BEAUTIFUL PIG.
( snorts like pig )
OKAY, ALL RIGHT.
I JUST SPENT
THE ENTIRE AFTERNOON
LOOKING FOR A PRESENT
FOR KATHY
THAT WOULD BE
BETTER THAN THE RABBIT.
ANY LUCK?
OH, YEAH.
I FOUND THIS GREAT PLACE CALLED
"INVISIBLE THINGS FOR KATHY."
CAN YOU GIVE ME A HAND
WITH ALL THIS STUFF?
ALL RIGHT, LOOK.
WHY DON'T YOU JUST
RETURN THE BOOK
LET JOEY GIVE HER THE CLOCK PEN
AND YOU GET HER SOMETHING
WORSE THAN THAT LIKE...
A REGULAR PEN.
SHE'S REALLY GOING
TO LOVE THIS, YOU KNOW?
THE BOTTOM LINE IS
I WANT HER TO HAVE IT
EVEN IF I DON'T
GET TO BE THE ONE
WHO GIVES IT TO HER.
OH, HONEY,
THAT'S SO SWEET.
YEAH? YOU DON'T THINK
IT'S JUST PATHETIC?
OOH! PATHETIC.
HEY! I'M MEETING KATHY
IN TEN MINUTES.
I BEEN LOOKING
ALL OVER FOR YOU.
WHERE?
OUR PLACE, THE HALL! I...
I GOT SOMETHING FOR HER.
IT'S A BOOK.
A BOOK?
( gasps )
IS IT, LIKE, A BOOK
THAT'S ALSO A SAFE?
IT'S A BOOK;
JUST A BOOK.
IT'S AN EARLY EDITION
OF THE VELVETEEN RABBIT.
IT WAS HER FAVORITE
BOOK AS A KID.
SO, UH, JUST LET ME KNOW
IF SHE LIKES IT, OKAY?
OH, YOU GOT IT.
THANKS, MAN.
THANKS FOR DOING THIS.
I OWE YOU ONE.
HEY! THERE WASN'T CHANGE
FROM THAT 20, WAS THERE?
NO. IT CAME OUT
TO AN EVEN 20.
WOW. THAT'S ALMOST AS MUCH
AS A NEW BOOK.
( brisk piano )
♪ JEEPERS, CREEPERS ♪
♪ WHERE'D YOU GET
THOSE PEEPERS? ♪
♪ JEEPERS, CREEPERS... ♪
YOU DIDN'T GET
THE MONEY, DID YOU?
MAYBE I CAN TRY AT INTERMISSION?
OH, PHOEBE, COME ON.
LET'S JUST GO.
NO! HEY, WE'RE NOT LEAVING
TILL WE GET PAID.
WHO DOES SHE THINK SHE IS?
ENOUGH IS ENOUGH.
HEY, WIDOW.
♪ COME ON ALONG
AND LISTEN TO ♪
WIDOW?
♪ THE LULLABY OF... ♪
EXCUSE ME. EXCUSE ME!
THANKS.
UM, CLEARLY, THIS IS
A VERY, VERY HARD TIME FOR YOU
UM, BUT WE PROVIDED A SERVICE
AND WE DESERVE TO BE PAID
BECAUSE YOU ATE THAT SERVICE
AND, UM, WE ARE NOT
LEAVING HERE
UNTIL WE ARE PAID EVERY PENNY,
'CAUSE YOU KNOW WHAT, LADY?
WE'RE PART-TIME CATERERS
AND WE HAVE NO PLACE ELSE TO GO.
OH, ALL RIGHT.
I'LL GET MY BAG.
GOOD.
I'M GOING TO LEAVE
SOME CARDS HERE.
PLEASE THINK OF US
FOR YOUR NEXT EVENT.
SO YOU WANT
TO COME INSIDE?
( hesitantly ):
YES.
( firmly ):
YES, I DO.
I'LL BE RIGHT BACK.
MAKE YOURSELF COMFORTABLE.
GUESS WHO?
UH... DEPARTMENT
OF SANITATION?
IT'S ME.
OH. OH.
OH!
WHAT?
OH, CHERYL!
OH, ROSS!
OH! OH!
( wails )
OH... GOD.
( rustling )
( yells )
OH, NO! NO!
NO, NO, NO!
IT'S MY...
IT'S MY HAMSTER!
IT'S MITZI!
OH, MY GOD. I'M SO SORRY.
I MUST HAVE FREAKED OUT.
OH, THANK GOD,
IT'S NOT MITZI.
( sighs )
IT'S JUST A RAT.
I DID IT.
OH! I FINISHED IT!
I DID IT ALL BY MYSELF!
AND THERE'S NOBODY TO HUG.
( clattering )
MOVE!
HEY. HEY, YOU GUYS!
I FINISHED THE CROSSWORD
BY MYSELF. HUG ME.
YAY! THAT'S SO GOOD.
CONGRATULATIONS.
THANK YOU.
HOW'D THE CATERING GO?
OH, IT WAS GREAT.
THE WIDOW WOULDN'T PAY
SO PHOEBE YELLED
AT HER TILL SHE DID.
YEAH. I'M A HARD-ASS.
AND I'M A WUSS.
AND WE SHOULD BE PARTNERS.
YEAH-- HARDASS AND WUSS.
WE COULD FIGHT CRIME.
WAIT A MINUTE, PHOEBE.
WE SHOULD BE PARTNERS.
WE SHOULD BE CATERING PARTNERS.
THINK ABOUT IT.
YOU'RE NOT WORKING
RIGHT NOW
AND WE HAVE SUCH
A GREAT TIME TOGETHER.
OKAY.
I COOK, YOU TAKE
CARE OF THE MONEY.
OH! IT'LL BE LIKE
I HAVE A WIFE IN THE '50s.
( both screaming )
HEY.
HEY. HOW'D IT GO?
HOW'D SHE LIKE THE GIFT?
MAN, SHE LOVED IT.
SHE'S SHOWING MONICA
AND RACHEL NOW.
OH, YEAH? THAT'S GREAT.
LISTEN. I GOT
TO TELL YOU.
I FEEL KIND OF BAD
TAKING CREDIT FOR THIS
BECAUSE, MAN,
AM I GOING TO GET
A LOT OF CREDIT FOR THIS.
( both chuckle )
HEY.
HEY. HAPPY BIRTHDAY.
THANK YOU.
YOU KNOW, UH, CHANDLER
GOT YOU A GIFT, TOO.
NO, HE DIDN'T.
YEAH, HE DID. LOOK.
IT'S RIGHT THERE ON THE COUNTER.
HO-HO-HO!
HAPPY BIRTHDAY.
I'M SORRY.
YOU REALLY DIDN'T HAVE TO.
WOW.
SEE, YOU THINK
IT'S JUST A PEN
BUT THEN YOU TURN IT OVER
AND IT'S ALSO A CLOCK.
YEAH.
NO. THIS IS GREAT.
THANK YOU, CHANDLER.
OH. Y-YEAH.
AH.
WANT TO GO TO BED?
I'LL BE IN
IN A MINUTE.
OKAY.
OH, UH, DON'T FORGET
YOUR COUPON.
GOOD NIGHT.
UM, THANK YOU FOR THE GIFT.
OH, UH, YEAH.
I JUST KNEW THAT SOMETIMES
WHEN YOU'RE WRITING
YOU-YOU DON'T ALWAYS KNOW
THE EXACT TIME.
NO. I DIDN'T MEAN THE PEN.
THANK YOU FOR THE BOOK.
UH, THE BOOK?
THE VELVETEEN RABBIT?
I HAVE THE FEELING YOU HAD
SOMETHING TO DO WITH IT.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
WELL, WHEN JOEY
GAVE IT TO ME
HE SAID, "THIS IS 'CAUSE
I KNOW YOU LIKE RABBITS
AND I KNOW
YOU LIKE CHEESE."
( sighs )
THANKS. I LOVE IT.
AND I KNOW HOW HARD
IT MUST HAVE BEEN
FOR YOU TO FIND.
( mutters ):
OH, WELL.
BY THE WAY, IN CASE YOU
MISSED THAT, THAT SOUND WAS:
( mutters ):
OH, WELL.
YOU MUST REALLY LIKE JOEY
TO GO TO ALL THAT
TROUBLE FOR HIM.
OH, YEAH! HE'S MY...
HE'S MY BEST FRIEND.
OH, WELL.
GOOD NIGHT.
HEY, THAT COUPON EXPIRES,
YOU KNOW.
( both giggle )
( knocking )
HI. UH, YOU DON'T KNOW ME.
I'M MONICA GELLER,
ROSS'S SISTER.
OH, YEAH. YOU KNOW,
IT'S TOO BAD
THAT DIDN'T WORK OUT.
YEAH. ANYWAY, HE TOLD ME
ABOUT YOUR APARTMENT
AND, UM, WELL...
I COULDN'T SLEEP
THINKING ABOUT IT.
SO, UH, WOULD IT BE OKAY
IF I CLEANED IT?
NO?